
export const quizQuestions_8 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What is the primary purpose of testing in a React application?',
      choices: [
        'To ensure the code is syntactically correct',
        'To verify the visual appearance of components',
        'To ensure the application functions correctly and reliably',
        'To validate the integration with external libraries',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'To ensure the application functions correctly and reliably',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which library is commonly used for unit testing React components?',
      choices: ['Mocha', 'Jest', 'Chai', 'Enzyme'],
      correctAnswer: 'Jest',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is snapshot testing in Jest?',
      choices: [
        'Testing the applications performance',
        'Capturing and comparing component snapshots',
        'Testing components with complex state logic',
        'Testing components in isolation',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Capturing and comparing component snapshots',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the `render` function in testing React components with Jest?',
      choices: [
        'To create a visual representation of the component',
        'To simulate user interactions',
        'To render the component in a virtual DOM',
        'To check if the component is mounted successfully',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'To render the component in a virtual DOM',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the role of the `act` function in React testing?',
      choices: [
        'To create asynchronous tests',
        'To act as a testing assertion',
        'To simulate component interactions',
        'To synchronize test behavior with component updates',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'To synchronize test behavior with component updates',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does Jest`s `describe` function do in a testing suite?',
      choices: [
        'It describes the purpose of the test suite',
        'It defines the test suite setup and teardown',
        'It groups related test cases together',
        'It creates a new Jest instance',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'It groups related test cases together',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the `it` function in Jest?',
      choices: [
        'It marks a test as incomplete',
        'It defines the test case and contains the test logic',
        'It imports external test utilities',
        'It runs the entire test suite',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'It defines the test case and contains the test logic',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the significance of the `beforeEach` function in Jest testing?',
      choices: [
        'It runs once before all test cases in a suite',
        'It runs once after all test cases in a suite',
        'It runs before each test case in a suite',
        'It sets up the Jest environment',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'It runs before each test case in a suite',
    },
    {
      question: 'What type of testing focuses on interactions between different components in a React application?',
      choices: [
        'Unit testing',
        'Integration testing',
        'End-to-end testing',
        'Snapshot testing',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Integration testing',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of a mocking library, such as `jest.mock`?',
      choices: [
        'To create fake components for testing',
        'To simulate asynchronous behavior',
        'To replace external dependencies with mocks',
        'To create realistic API calls in tests',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'To replace external dependencies with mocks',
    },
  ],
}